很快便來到今天音樂會的尾聲
就是大合唱
事不宜遲，我們將時間交給全體表演的小朋友、家長
以及特別嘉賓林一峰
為我們唱出今晚的大合唱《You Raise Me Up》，有請
Woo ...
When I am down and, oh my soul, so weary;
When troubles come and my heart burdened be;
Then, I am still and wait here in the silence,
Until you come and sit awhile with me.
You raise me up, so I can stand on mountains;
You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas;
I am strong, when I am on your shoulders;
You raise me up: To more than I can be.
There is no life - no life without its hunger;
Each restless heart beats so imperfectly;
But when you come and I am filled with wonder,
Sometimes, I think I glimpse eternity.
You raise me up, so I can stand on mountains;
You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas;
I am strong, when I am on your shoulders;
You raise me up: To more than I can be.
You raise me up …
(You raise me up, so I can stand on mountains;)
(You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas;)
And I am strong, when I am on your shoulders;
(I am strong, when I am on your shoulders;)
You raise me up: To more than I can be.
You raise me up …
(You raise me up, so I can stand on mountains;)
(You raise me up, to walk on stormy seas;)
I am strong, when I am on your shoulders;
You raise me up: To more than I can be.
謝謝今晚所有參與表演的小朋友
謝謝表演嘉賓林一峰
謝謝唐校長
我們現在有請（合唱團董事會主席）何校長上台
與唐校長一起頒贈紀念品
予今晚的特別嘉賓林一峰先生
有請何校長
再次感謝林一峰今晚為我們表演
大家給他一點掌聲好嗎
我們亦有請眾多合唱團的董事上台
（與）我們一起拍大合照
有請眾多合唱團董事